[
    {
      "question": " _________________ is a billing and account management service.",
  
      "option1": "  Amazon Mechanical Turk",
  
      "option2": "  Amazon Elastic MapReduce",
  
      "option3": "  Amazon DevPay",
  
      "option4": "  Multi-Factor Authentication",
  
      "answer": " Amazon DevPay"
},
    {
        "question": "  ________________ is the central application in the AWS portfolio.",
    
        "option1": " Amazon Simple Queue Service",
    
        "option2": " Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud",
    
        "option3": " Amazon Simple Notification Service",
    
        "option4": "  All of the above",
    
        "answer": " Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud"
      },
      {
        "question": " Amazon Web Services falls into which of the following cloud-computing category ?",
    
        "option1": " Platform as a Service",
    
        "option2": " Software as a Service",
    
        "option3": " Infrastructure as a Service",
    
        "option4": " Back-end as a Service",
    
        "answer": " Infrastructure as a Service"
      },
      {
        "question": " How many buckets can you create in AWS by default?",
    
        "option1": "  100 buckets",
    
        "option2": "  200 buckets",
    
        "option3": "  110 buckets",
    
        "option4": "  125 buckets",
    
        "answer": " 100 buckets"
      },
      {
        "question": " What are the different types of instances ?",
    
        "option1": " General purpose",
    
        "option2": " Computer Optimized",
    
        "option3": " Storage Optimized",
    
        "option4": " All of the above",
    
        "answer": " All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": " What are the advantages of auto-scaling ?",
    
        "option1": " Better availability",
    
        "option2": "  Offers fault tolerance",
    
        "option3": "  Better cost management",
    
        "option4": "  All of the above",
    
        "answer": "  All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": " The types of AMI provided by AWS are:",
    
        "option1": " Instance store backed",
    
        "option2": " EBS backed",
    
        "option3": " Both 1 & 2",
    
        "option4": " None of the above",
    
        "answer": " Both 1 & 2"
      },
      {
        "question": " Storage classes available with Amazon s3 are",
    
        "option1": " Amazon S3 standard",
    
        "option2": " Amazon S3 standard-infrequent Access",
    
        "option3": " Amazon Glacier",
    
        "option4": " All of the above",
    
        "answer": " All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the following statement is wrong about Amazon S3 ?",
    
        "option1": " Amazon S3 provides large quantities of reliable storage that is highly protected",
    
        "option2": " Amazon S3 is highly available",
    
        "option3": " Amazon S3 is highly reliable",
    
        "option4": " All of the above",
    
        "answer": " Amazon S3 is highly reliable"
      },
      {
        "question": " Amazon S3 is which type of storage service ?",
    
        "option1": " Block",
    
        "option2": " Object",
    
        "option3": " Simple",
    
        "option4": " Secure",
    
        "answer": " Object"
      }
    
    
    
]